http://www.ecosafenatural.com/privacy/

Contact us to discuss your next project
Privacy
Privacy Statement
EcoSafe Natural Products Inc. (Ecosafe) is committed to protecting your privacy. By using the EcoSafe website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
EcoSafe collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. EcoSafe also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by EcoSafe Natural Products Inc. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by EcoSafe for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the EcoSafe website.
Use of your Personal Information
EcoSafe collects and uses your personal information to operate the EcoSafe website and deliver the services you have requested. EcoSafe also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from EcoSafe and its affiliates. EcoSafe may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
EcoSafe may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to EcoSafe and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
EcoSafe keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within EcoSafe, in order to determine what EcoSafe services are of most interest.
EcoSafe websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on EcoSafe or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of EcoSafe; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of EcoSafe, or the public.
Changes to this Statement
EcoSafe will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. EcoSafe encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how EcoSafe is protecting your information.
Contact Information
EcoSafe welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that EcoSafe has not adhered to this Statement, please contact EcoSafe at research@ecosafenatural.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
© 2020 EcoSafe Natural Products Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Web Design and Development by Upanup
Call Now Button
